Achieve Your Goals

Products

About Herbalife

* Achieve Your Goals
* Products
* About Herbalife

    * [Carbohydrates and Exercise: Why You Need Carbs If You’re Active](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/carbohydrates-and-exercise-why-you-need-carbs-if-you-are-active)

    * [Fast-Track Your Fitness Results with a Balanced Exercise Plan](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/fast-track-your-fitness-results-with-a-balanced-exercise-plan)

    * [3 Key Benefits of Protein for Health and Athletic Performance](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/three-key-benefits-of-protein-for-health-performance)
        
    * [Workout Supplements: What to Take Before, During and After Exercise](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/workout-supplements-what-to-take-before-during-and-after-exercise)

    * [Know Your Macros: How Protein, Carbs and Fat Fuel Athletic Performance](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/know-your-macros-how-protein-carbs-fat-fuel-athletic-performance)

    * [Best Oils to Have in Your Kitchen: Understanding Heart-Healthy Fats](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/best-oils-to-have-in-your-kitchen-understanding-heart-healthy-fats)

    * [Herbalife24® Liftoff®: A Boost for Everyday and Professional Athletes](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/herbalife24-liftoff-a-boostb-or-everyday-and-professional-athletes)
        
    * [Meal Replacement Shakes vs. Protein Supplements: When to Use One Over the Other?](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/meal-replacements-protein-shakes)
        
    * [How to Build Muscle Effectively: The Role of Protein, Diet and Exercise](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/building-muscle)

    * [How to Control Hunger: 5 Proven Strategies to Curb Your Appetite](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/control-hunger)

    * [How Much Protein Do You Need Per Day? Here’s How to Calculate Your Intake Needs](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/how-much-protein-do-you-need-per-day)

    * [​​Understanding GLP-1 Weight-Loss Drugs and How Herbalife Fills the Nutritional Gap​](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/articles/understanding-glp-1-weight-loss-drugs-and-how-herbalife-fills-the-nutritional-gap)

    * [Apricot Mango Smoothie with HERBALIFE V Plant-Based Greens Booster](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/recipes/apricot-mango-smoothie-with-herbalide-v-plant-based-greens-booster)
        
    * [Herbalife Sponsored Athlete Heather Jackson’s Banana Split Shake](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/recipes/herbalife-sponsored-athlete-heather-jacksons-banana-split-shake)

    * [Mixed Berries Smoothie Bowl with HERBALIFE V Plant-Based Protein Shake](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/wellness-resources/recipes/mixed-berries-smoothie-bowl-with-herbalife-v-plant-based-protein-shake)

Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

1. [Privacy Policy](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/footer/privacy-policy)
2. [Cookie Policy](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/footer/cookie-policy)
3. [Terms of Use](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/footer/terms-of-use)
4. [Ethics and Compliance](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/footer/ethics-and-compliance)
5. [Refund policy](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/footer/refund-policy)
6. [Herbalife Terms and Conditions of Purchase](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/footer/supplier-terms)
7. [Herbalife Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/footer/herbalife-consumer-health-data-privacy-policy)

Privacy Policy
==============

Our Products

About Herbalife

Get Help

For Distributors

Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information/Opt-out of Targeted Advertising

Herbalife is a Proud Member of the [Direct Selling Association](https://www.dsa.org/about/direct-selling) and a Signatory to the [DSA Code of Ethics](https://www.dsa.org/consumerprotection/code-of-ethics). Copyright ©2024 Herbalife International of America, Inc. No reproduction in whole or in part without written permission. All Rights Reserved. All trademarks and product images exhibited on this site, unless otherwise indicated, are the property of Herbalife International, Inc.

      [

United States](https://www.herbalife.com/en-us/location-selector)
